FARZIN GHAHERI

Frontend Developer

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A successful developer with extensive analytical skills. Highly talented, driven and flexible graphic designer with a proven record of delivering creative and innovative design solutions. Able to work as part of a team with printers, copywriters, photographers, game designers, other designers, web developers and marketing specialists

CONTACT

PHONE: +60-178759878

EMAIL: f.ghaheri@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Chess Movie Book

LANGUAGE

Persian (Fluent) English (Fluent) Bahasa Melayu (Intermediate)

HONORS AND AWARDS

Won gold medal in ITEX 2016 (Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia) (Co-operated in mobile game design)

ICDL (International Computer Driving License).

EDUCATION

University Pendidikan Sultan Idris (MSc Game-based learning) Malaysia 2015 - 2018

Limkokwing University (BSc (Hons) Information Technology) Malaysia 2013 - 2015

Asia Pacific University (Diploma in game design) Malaysia 2009 - 2012

WORK EXPERIENCE

Yantrik SDN BHD [Developer and Designer]

2018 - 2020

- Developed web application by using angular.
- Developed Mobile app by using Ionic.

Part-time Freelance, Kuala Lumpur [Developer and Designer]

2017 - 2018

- Designed and built website by using angular.
- Designed application for restaurant in Iran by using angular.
- Designed logos and leaflets for some companies in Malaysia and other
- Developed web application by using angular.

Fanavari Jahani, Kerman-Iran [Developer and Designer]

2001 - 2008

- Designed logos, flyers, signboards and website interface
- Developed inventory for companies by VB
- Cooperated to develop mobile games by C# in Visual basic for Unity
- Developed mobile game by Java Applet
- Designed animation by Swish MAX
- 3D design by 3DMAX

TOOLS & SKILLS

Methodology Agile, Waterfall

Operating Systems Windows, Unix, Linux, Android, iOS

C#, .Net, React, Vue.js, Angular 7, HTML, VB, Java Script, CSS, Node.js Languages

Platform Google Cloud Platform, Amazon, Azure,

Alibaba, Cloud, On Premise

Databases SQL Server

Adobe XD, Photoshop, In-design, Design

Illustrator, Swish Max, 3D Animation